翻译：小布拿拿      红豆包      Tiogy
翻译&校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
《开心汉堡店》第五季第十一集
窈窕除虫女
除虫害公司
数学测验又得了个D
Another D on a math test.
如果下次考试我不能得B
And if I don't get at least a B on the next one,
就得参加数学补习了
I've got to go to remedial math.
数学补习
Remedial math, huh?
补习第一天
On your first day in there,
记得去偷最年长孩子的铅笔
steal the biggest kid's pencil.
是的  削尖了再还回去
Yeah, and then sharpen it and give it back.
让我怎么和我未来的孙孩儿们交代
What'll I tell my grandchildren?
我以前数学很差
I used to be bad at math.
可怜的外祖母
Oh, Grandma.
我不会参加数学补习的
I'm not going to remedial math,
因为我要找一个家教
because I'm going to get a tutor
让他教我现在的老师没能教我的知识
who will teach me what my teacher could not.
不明白你为啥冲我们嚷嚷
I don't know why we're getting yelled at.
你猜这周末是什么节日  鲍鲍
You know what's this weekend, Bobby?
-是情人节哎  -糟糕
- Valentine's Day. - Oh, crap.
我不是说这个节日很糟糕  琳
I-I mean, I-I don't mean crap, Lin.
我知道你喜欢情人节
I-I know you love Valentine's Day,
我只是觉得我从来就没做对过
I just feel like I never get it quite right.
-是的  你不行  -的确  你逊毙了
- No, you do not. - No, you're horrible at it.
不过还有那么几次
Well, I mean, a couple times,
我送了你很好的礼物
I got you something nice.
-还记得我送你的换机油吗  -记得
- Remember I got the oil change? - Right.
-给车使的  -记得  是的
- For the car? - Right, yeah.
-特意送你的  -是啊  真"贴心"
- That was for you. - You did that, that was nice.
-是的  -今年
- Yeah. - This year,
你不必再担心啦
you don't have to worry,
因为我都准备好了
'cause I got it all figured out.
你看
Ta-da!
这是什么
What is it?
为庆祝耶稣降生的一种倒数计时月历
从12月1日起  每天在对应日期打开一扇门  之后往往有惊喜
情人节版耶稣降临日历
It's a Valentine's Advent calendar.
今年我们要过情人周
This year we're doing Valentine's Days.
情人周
Valentine's Days?
不必再为要把
Say good-bye to the pressure
所有的浪漫压缩到一天而压力山大啦
of being super-romantic on one day,
今年我们要在情人节前
and say hello to being somewhat-romantic
把浪漫匀给很多天
for a bunch of days leading up to the big V.
-太好了  -每扇小门背后
- Yeah! - Behind each little door is a romantic activity
都有我策划的浪漫惊喜
that I've already thought of.
-你都计划好了  -没错
- Oh, you planned stuff. - That's right!
好吧  这样更好
All right, uh, that sounds better.
是吧  打开第一个节日吧  鲍鲍
Right? Open up day one, Bobby.
来吧  我来开
Come on, l-let me open it.
-不  泰迪  起开  -来嘛  让我开
- No. Teddy, get off it! - Come on, let me open it.
-泰迪  给...  -让我开嘛
- Teddy, Teddy, give it... - Just let me open it,
-你可以开其它日子的  -泰迪  放手
- You can open up the other days. - Teddy, let it go.
好吧
Okay, uh...
"性感厨房"
"Sexy cooking."
性感厨房  我就知道
Sexy cooking... I knew it.
是的
Yeah.
我不太明白这具体是什么意思
I don't exactly know what that means,
但如果这意味着我不会毁了情人节
but if it means I'm not gonna screw up Valentine's Day,
那我加入
then I am in.
我喜欢  我们都加入
I love it. We're in.
罗莎
Rosa.
罗莎  罗莎
Rosa, Rosa.
-达瑞尔  -怎么了
- Darryl! - What?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help...
你能帮我补数学吗
Could you tutor me at math?
不接新客户
Not taking on new clients.
我给人补习之后和玩电子游戏之前的时间
All my post-tutoring, pre-video-game free time
都要交给机器人
is going to robotics.
我正在帮我爷爷设计一个机器人陪护
I'm building a companion robot for my grandpa.
能给他吃药并播放爵士乐
It gives him pills and plays jazz.
但如果我得不到帮助
But if I don't get help,
我就得参加数学补习了
I've got to go to remedial math.
真可怜  祝好运
That's tough. Good luck.
等等  周六教我怎么样
Wait, what about tutoring me on Saturday?
我不打算去情人节舞会  也许...
I'm not going to the Valentine's Day dance, so maybe...
你觉得我是个呆子  所以我也不会去吗
And you assume because I'm a nerd, I'm not going, either?
什么  抱歉  我以为你不去
What? Oh, I'm sorry, I assumed you weren't going
完全是因为别的原因
for a totally different reason.
是的  我不去
Yeah, I'm not going.
对啊  呆子情侣
That's it... double nerd.
跟我来  我们私下谈谈
Come with me, we got to talk in private.
如果你当我情人节舞伴
I'll tutor you if you'll be my date
我就给你当家教
to the Valentine's dance.
达瑞尔  我真是受宠若惊
Oh, Darryl, I'm flattered,
但我的心几乎都给了小吉米
but I'm semi-involved with someone... Jimmy Jr.
他现在还没有那么喜欢我
He's semi-not-involved with me right now,
但我们会在一起的
but we're working through it.
不  我不是真的想和你跳舞
No, I don't really want to go to the dance with you.
我想和罗莎・巴蒂斯塔一起去
I want to go with Rosa Batista.
那你为什么不邀请罗莎
Then why don't you ask Rosa?
我不能  我配不上她[不是我阵营的]
I can't... she's out of my league.
我读初一  她上初二
I'm in seventh grade, she's in eighth.
她肯定还把我当那个
I think she still sees me as the little boy
在滑梯尿尿的二年级小孩
that peed down the slide in second grade.
那是你啊
Oh, that was you?
不是尿在秋千上么
I heard it was off a swing.
可能是撒了两滴到秋千上
Some of it may have gotten on the swing.
听我说  还记得去年舞会
But listen, do you remember who won Cupid's Couple
谁赢了初一初二级的丘比特情侣吗
at last year's seventh-eighth grade Valentine's dance?
迈克尔・卡利什和特蕾西・施瓦兹  对吗
Michael Carlish and Tracy Schwartz, right?
他们分手后
And after they broke up,
初一的迈克尔・卡利什开始约初二的
seventh-grade Michael Carlish started dating eighth-grade...
珍妮・特斯塔
Jenny Testa.
只要成为丘比特情侣  分手后
Whoever wins Cupid's Couple can date anyone
就可以约任何想约的人
they want when they break up.
如果我们假装约会  我们就能赢
If we fake-date, we could win.
然后我们假装分手
And then if we fake break-up,
我就可以约罗莎了
I could date Rosa,
你可以去约小吉米了
and you could date Jimmy Jr.
但大家为什么要选你和我当丘比特情侣呢
But why would students vote you and me to be Cupid's Couple?
因为我们是呆子情侣
Because of the double-nerd angle.
-我不是呆子  -其实你是
- I'm not a nerd. - You kind of are.
-我不是  -我们太可爱了  不会输的
- I'm not. - We'll be too adorable to lose.
负负得正
A negative times a negative is a positive.
-没这回事  -这个等补习的时候再教你
- That can't be right. - We'll cover that in tutoring.
那就这么说定了
So, do we have a deal?
感觉愚弄感情不大好
Feels kind of wrong to mess with love.
小吉米哦
Jimmy Jr.
我们得小心点
We'd have to be careful.
这么多浪漫喜剧观影经验告诉我
I've seen enough romantic comedies to know
你很可能会爱上我
you're probably gonna fall for me.
我不会爱上你的
I won't fall for you.
好吧  不过你还是有可能会爱上我
Okay, it's just that you're probably gonna fall for me.
-千万别  -我不会的
- Don't. - I won't.
-很好  一定要忍着  -没那必要
- Good, fight that feeling. - I won't need to.
好吧  假男友
Okay, fake boyfriend,
我们假装谈场恋爱吧
let's fake do this.
你的手和你额头一样黏黏的
Your hand is sweaty like a forehead.
我知道  我就是这样
I know. It's an issue.
天哪  你们现在是情侣吗
Oh, my God, are you two a couple now?
-你自己琢磨[算算]吧  -我不要
- You do the math. - No.
好吧  我们是情侣了
Yeah, we are.
我的乖乖
Well, nibble my dibble.
你们约会有多久了
How long have y'all been going out?
-一个月  -今天刚开始
- A month. - Since today.
今天刚开始  但比那更早
Since today, but earlier.
我从来没怎么注意过你们俩
I never really thought about either of you that much,
但你们真是可爱的一对
but you guys make a cute couple.
是的  你们俩单独看谁都不咋样
Yeah, it's like neither of you are cute,
但在一起就很可爱
but together you're cute.
我们都戴眼镜
We're both humans who wear glasses!
小点声  达瑞尔
Volume, Darryl.
是的  伙计  我们就在你边上呢
Yeah, man, we're right here.
你还好吗  伙计
You all right, buddy?
达瑞尔  亲爱的
Darryl, sweetie,
你能和我来一下
will you come with me for a sec
帮我检查一下头发里的虱子吗
and check my hair for lice?
-好吧  -我们马上回来
- Okay. - We'll be right back.
我手心出了好多汗啊
I'm losing so much water out of my palms!
这样下去我明早就得脱水而死了
I'll be dead by morning!
打起精神来  达瑞尔
Pull it together, Darryl!
也许我想的这个主意不怎么样
Maybe I was wrong about this.
我不知道如何当男友
I don't know how to be a boyfriend.
你从来没有约会过
You haven't dated anyone.
而我只约会过两个半男生
And I've only dated two-and-a-half boys,
但我对男生和感情的事颇有研究
but I've thought about boys and relationships a lot.
超有研究
Like, a lot.
-真的超有研究  -好吧
- I mean, a lot. - Okay.
这样怎么样
So, how about this?
你教我数学
You'll be my math tutor,
-我教你如何做男朋友  -好吧
- and I'll be your boyfriend tutor. - Okay.
比如  如果你不知道说什么
Like, if you don't know what to say,
就轻轻搂着我
just give me a tiny side-hug.
天哪  好吧  不是这样
Oh, God. Okay, not like that.
还不错
Decent hug,
但下次抱时别出声
but do it silently next time.
好消息  我们都没长虱子
Good news, neither of us have lice.
再和大家打次招呼
So, hello again, everyone.
你们在一起好般配啊
You guys look so cute together.
-多谢  罗莎  -不客气
- Thanks, Rosa. - You're welcome.
再见
B-Bye.
-再见  -再见
- B-Bye. - Oh, bye. Bye.
那是达瑞尔和蒂娜在拉手吗
Are Darryl and Tina holding hands?
蒂娜可从来没正眼瞧过达瑞尔
Tina hasn't pined after Darryl for one second.
要知道她可瞧上过不少人
And that girl can pine.
琳  你能把这个给四号桌端去吗
Hey, Lin, can you take this to table four?
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
性感厨房
Sexy cooking.
好吧  好吧
Oh, okay, right.
-她成功了  -生奶油
- She got ya! - Whipped cream.
-很性感  有没有  -绝对有  -泰迪
- Sexy, right? - Very. - Teddy.
现在时间不太合适  琳
Now's not really the best time, Lin.
-来嘛  -现在是午饭高峰期呢
- Come here. - It's the lunch rush.
来嘛  来
Come on, come on.
还有  你能把汉堡送去四号桌吗
Also, can you take that burger to table four?
可以呀  还是你要找找看我藏在
I could, or you can try and find the strawberry
身上的草莓
I've hidden somewhere on my body.
你在说什么啊
Wh-What are you talking about?
*找呀找呀找草莓*
*Find the strawberry *
*找草莓*
*Strawberry trail *
不  不
No. I don't know.
现在不行
Not right now.
是不是在那里
Wait, is that it, right there?
你围裙口袋里
In your apron pocket?
那是在里面咯
So it's in there.
对  来拿
Yeah, come and get it.
那草莓已经脏了
Well, it's all dirty now,
你把脏抹布搭围裙口袋上了
'cause it's in your apron with a dirty dishrag.
是很"脏"[淫荡]
So dirty.
快点啦  都要软了
Hurry up, it's getting all mushy.
我现在不太想
Well, I don't really want to now,
-上面有抹布呢  -你肯定想的
- it has a dishrag on it. - Sure you do.
我真的不想
I really don't.
-我不想吃  -当然要吃
- I don't want that one. - You know you want to.
-不  -张嘴
- No. - Open up...
张嘴
Open up.
-不要  -好  那我先来一口
- No. - Fine, I'll take a nibble.
琳  你在呕了
Lin, you're gagging.
蒂娜  看来是刚补习完回来啊
Tina, hey, back from tutoring, I see.
-坐  我亲爱的姐姐  -好吧
- Have a seat, my sister. - Sure.
达瑞尔  你男友  你  他女友
So, Darryl, boyfriend, you, girlfriend?
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Really.
好吧  你赢了
Okay, you broke me!
达瑞尔和我是假装在约会
Darryl and I are pretending we're dating
目的是在舞会上赢得"丘比特情侣"的称号
so we can win Cupid's Couple at the dance,
然后我们想约谁就能约谁了
and then we can go out with whoever we want,
我还不用上学校的数学补习班
and I stay in normal math.
我就知道跟数学有关
I knew math was responsible!
拜托别说出去
Please don't tell.
如果有人知道我们是假的
If anyone knows we're faking,
我们就赢不了了
then we won't win.
行  那贿赂我们一下
Right. Bribe, please.
好吧  胜出的一对
Okay. Well, the winners of Cupid's Couple
会得到价值50美元的酸奶礼券
geta $50 frozen yogurt gift card.
如果我们赢了  就给你们
I guess you guys can have that if we win.
你说有礼券的时候我就同意了
You had me at "Gets a $50 frozen yogurt gift card."
男友应该时时夸奖自己的女友
Now, a boyfriend should always give his girlfriend compliments.
比如说  你可以夸我
Like, you could tell me
用了一次就把柜子打开了
I did a great job of opening my locker
很厉害
on the first try.
这个也要夸奖
I should compliment you on that?
尤其是这个
Especially that.
我的柜子很有想法  这点我虽然很尊重
My locker has a mind of its own, which I respect,
但有时我确实需要拿下书
but also sometimes I just need to get my books.
好吧
okay.
你用一次就把柜子打开了
Hey, great job opening your locker
-真棒  蒂娜  -谢谢
- on the first try, Tina. - Oh, thanks.
-真甜蜜啊  -就是
- That is some sweet talk. - I know, right?
他们能在对方的镜片上看到自己
It's so cute how their glasses reflect off each other.
像两面永无止境的镜子
Yeah, like two mirrors that go on forever.
无尽的东西总让我汗毛倒立
Infinite stuff trips me out!
天呐  你背上有只蜘蛛
Oh, no, there's a spider on your back.
快弄下来  弄下来
Get it off! Get it off!
不是真的  是我的手
No, it's not real, it's my hand.
只是个游戏  我们专属的游戏
It's a cute game we play, it's our thing.
可我讨厌蜘蛛  甲虫行吗
But I hate spiders, could it be a beetle?
当然  天呐
Sure. Oh, no.
你背上有只甲虫
There's a beetle on your back.
虫子游戏简直堪比抱抱了
Bugs are, like, the new hugs.
看来丘比特是射对人了  对吧
Cupid sure hit that couple right in the rump, huh?
这是世纪之恋啊
It's the romance of the century!
和酸奶一点关系都没有
And it has nothing to do with yogurt.
情人节舞会
今晚和你在一起很愉快
I'm having a really good time with you tonight.
我觉得别人没听到
I don't think everyone heard you.
-得大声喊  盖过音乐  -哦对
- You got to yell over the music. - Oh, right.
今晚和你在一起很愉快
I'm having a really good time with you tonight.
天  看克洛伊和扎克的慢舞
Oh, man, look at Chloe and Zack slow dance.
真的好慢
They are so slow!
动都没怎么动
they're barely moving.
这让我们怎么跟他们比
How do we compete with that?
我们不能让他们赢
We cannot let them win Cupid's Couple.
等等  我知道了
Hold on, I got a good idea.
大家情人节过的开心吗
Hey, who's having a great Valentine's Day?
我过得比大家都开心
Well, I'm having a greater time,
因为我有世上最好的女朋友
because I'm here with the number one girlfriend in the world.
蒂娜・贝尔彻
Ti-na Bel-cher!
嗨
Hi.
我也想有人能这样喊出我的名字
I want someone to stretch out my name like that.
乔丝玲
Joce-lynn...!
DJ  来首慢歌
Deejay, slow-jam me.
*姑娘*
*Girl... *
*多希望*
*I wish you were *
*和你共度每一课堂*
*In all my classes *
*当我们亲吻对方*
*And when we kiss *
*我们的眼镜也碰上*
*We hit our glasses *
*让我们*
*Now let's *
*慢舞一曲*
*Slow dance *
*像蜂蜜糖浆*
*Like mol... asses... *
谢谢大家  玩得开心
Thank you, good night!
达瑞尔  你是怎么想出来的
Darryl, where did that come from?
女朋友都喜欢惊喜
Girlfriends like surprises.
你教我的
You taught me that.
知道怎样让我俩今晚达到巅峰吗
Hey, you know what might push us over the top right now?
-一个吻  -好主意
- A kiss. - Great idea.
来真一点的
Let's make this look real.
谁会想到达瑞尔是个完美男友
Who knew Darryl was total boyfriend material?
我知道
I know.
我之前不知道  现在知道了  你知道吗
I didn't know, but now I know, you know?
我们会赢的
We're gonna win this thing.
也许我们该再亲一次
We should probably kiss one more time.
免得刚有人系鞋带错过了
Just in case someone was tying their shoes and missed it.
也对  真周全
Right, good thinking.
准备好揭晓
So are you ready to see
情人节当天的惊喜了吗
what we got for actual Valentine's Day?
可能还没准备好
I don't know if I am ready.
这周过得挺艰难的
It's, uh, it's been a rough week.
前几次都是哑炮
We've had some misfires.
-也有一次真格的  -好吧
-And an actual fire, yeah. - Yeah.
泡泡浴
"Bubble Bath"!
泡泡浴应该不至于搞砸吧
Well, it's hard to mess up a bubble bath.
而且吉恩和露易丝都睡了
And Gene and Louise are asleep,
应该还不错
so that sounds good.
鲍鲍
Oh, Bobby.
嗨
Oh, hello, there.
快进来
Get in here, you.
超多泡泡的
It's nice and bubbly.
是很多泡泡
Yeah, there's a lot of bubbles.
我把一瓶都倒进来了
Yeah, I used the whole bottle.
你用了一瓶
You used the whole bottle?
一茶匙就够了啊
You're supposed to use, like, a teaspoon.
-太多不会有毒么  -不会的
- It's, like, toxic. - No.
好  好
All right, fine, fine, it's fine.
只是泡泡多了一点而已
It's just a lot of bubbles.
来吧  很好玩的
Come on, it's fun.
感觉都成浆糊了
It's like a paste in here.
是啊
Yeah, right?!
-像没加水似的  -看呐
- Feels like no water. - Look at that.
好吧  随便吧
Oh. Let's just go with it.
对啊
Yeah.
-但眼睛有点痛  -不重要啦
- But it stings. - Just ignore it.
弄到眼睛里会有点痛
Yeah, when it gets in your eyes, it stings.
别管它
Ignore it.
看看我
Come on, look at me.
琳  我得出去一下
I'm just gonna get out for a sec, Lin.
-不要  -我得洗个脸  吉恩
- No... I got to wash my face off. Gene!
我还以为你睡着了
I thought you were asleep.
我也以为
I thought I was, too.
但我的膀胱把我叫醒了
But then my bladder was, like, "Get up!"
现在啥情况
What's going on in here?
天  露易丝  你得出去
Oh, God, no, Louise, you got to get out.
我在尿尿
I'm peeing, but after,
尿完后我打算跳进去
I'm gonna make a sandwich
和爸妈来个三明治泡
and join Mom and Dad in the tub.
三明治泡怎么泡
What kind of sandwich?
琳  别
N-No, Lin, no.
我也想上厕所了
Well, now I got to pee.
用另外那个"马桶"啊
Use the second toilet.
爸妈  你们能不能出去一下
Mom, Dad, can you get out for a second?
你都在这里撒尿的吗
Do you pee in here?
-对啊  -你开玩笑的吧
- Yeah. - You're kidding me.
-没有  -我还在里面呢
- Well, no. - I'm in it.
对啊  所以我才要
Well, I... that's why I'm asking you
请你们出去一下
to please get out for just a minute.
第三对
Couple three.
第四对
And couple four.
获得丘比特情侣称号的是
All right, looks like the winner of Cupid's Couple is...
达瑞尔和蒂娜
Darryl and Tina!
英语形容情侣常用"love bird" 爱情鸟
先别急着飞走
Don't fly away,
你们还获得了50元"妈妈的味道"酸奶礼券
because you get a $50 gift card to Fro-Yo-Momma.
-我们成功了  -我知道
- We did it. - I know.
姑娘们都冲我笑呢
Girls are smiling at me.
那定理真的有效
The theorem's working.
为保万无一失  我们再亲最后一次吧
Let's kiss one more time to seal the deal.
可我们已经赢了
We already won.
罗莎呢  我找不到罗莎了
Where's Rosa? I can't see Rosa.
再来一次  看在过去的份上
And one more time, for old time's sake.
那个  我
All right, well, I...
再来一次
Okay one more.
我觉得
I guess...
等等  那个  再来一下
Wait, that... let's redo that one.
妈妈的味道酸奶店
那现在怎么搞
So, now what?
你和达瑞尔分手
You and Darryl break up?
然后小吉米就会屁颠颠跑来吗
And then Jimmy Jr. comes running?
还有罗莎  和我的数学成绩
And Rosa and my math scores,
达瑞尔是这么说的
according to Darryl's theory,
很有可能是真的
which is probably right,
他是我谈过的最聪明的男生了
since he's the smartest boy I've ever dated.
-假谈的  -对对  假谈的
- Fake dated. - Right, right. Fake dated.
那这分手  是君子之分还是小人之分
So, the breakup, is it gonna be classy or nasty?
绝对小人
Definitely nasty.
想知道这分手有几条限制吗
Want to know how many holds will be barred?
-三条吗  -一条都没有
- Three? - None.
那真是
Wow, that is...
够少的
so few.
你准备好了吗
You ready to do this?
也许我们应该再练习一下
Maybe we should practice more.
要不我们明天或下个月再分吧
What if we break up tomorrow or next month?
没事  我们可以的  好戏开演
Nah, we got this. Showtime.
给你的  亲爱的
For you, my sweets.
栀子花  我最爱的花吗
A gardenia? My favorite flower?
够了  我忍不了了
That's it! I can't take it anymore!
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你太善良太慷慨了
You're just too kind and generous.
-真让我恶心  -是吗
- It's making me sick. - Oh, yeah?
你人也太幽默
Well, you're too damn interesting,
快把我逼疯了
and it's driving me nuts.
这边发生什么事了
What's going on here?
丘比特情侣在吵架呢
Cupid's Couple is having a quarrel and a half.
你的魅力让我喘不过气
Your charisma is overwhelming me!
你特么就不能有一秒钟不那么有魅力吗
Why can't you be un-charming for one damn second?
我的魅力是无法改变的
I can't change how incredible I am.
就像你的杰出才华一样
Just like you can't change how phenomenal you are.
那也许  我们就不该在一起了
Then maybe we shouldn't date each other anymore.
你是想立马
You mean break up,
分手吗
effective immediately?
然后去和这所学校或其他学校的人约会吗
And date other people at this and/or other schools?
我们别无选择
It's our only choice!
真希望我知道该怎么驯服你  你这匹野马
I wish I knew how to tame you, you wild stallion!
-祝你安好  -你也是  深情的妙女子
- Have a great life. - You too, soulful wonder lady.
嗨  罗莎  抱歉让你看到这一幕
Hey, Rosa, sorry you had to see that.
小伙  真难为你了
Man, that was rough.
-你还好吗  达瑞尔  -我会好的
- Are you okay, Darryl? - I'll be all right.
-多谢关心  -不谢
- Thanks for asking. - You're welcome.
气氛真紧张
That was so intense.
我以为他们会永远在一起呢
I thought they were going to last forever and ever.
但居然在我们眼前决裂了
But instead they just imploded right before our eyes.
那  蒂娜又单身了吗
So, Tina's single again?
你干嘛问这个
Why do you want to know?
我  我又不在乎
I-I don't care.
小吉米喜欢蒂娜
Jimmy Jr. Likes Tina!
不  我不
No, I don't.
看罗莎和达瑞尔
Look at Rosa and Darryl.
可真迅速  那娃真是个天才
That happened fast. The kid's a genius.
是啊  他们打得真热火
Yeah, they're really hitting it off, those two.
他们真好啊
Good for them.
-嗨  蒂娜  -你好  小吉米
- Hey, Tina. - Hello, Jimmy Jr.
我们一群人准备今晚去打保龄球
A bunch of us are going bowling tonight,
既然你和达瑞尔已经分手了
and since you and Darryl aren't a couple anymore,
你要不要加入我们
I was wondering if you want to come.
保龄球  有人提到玉米片了吗
Bowling? Did someone say nachos?
我是在和蒂娜说话
I was kind of talking to Tina.
这是大孩子间的对话
This is just for older kids.
蒂娜坚持让我们随同
Tina is insisting that we go with her
还要把我们的费用也包了
and that she pay for us,
因为我们知道很多关于保龄球的事
because we know so much about bowling.
也许有人会认为太多了
Some might say too much.
-等下我不懂  你怎么可能知道  -关于
- Wait, I don't get it. How could you know - About
关于保龄球的事
too much about bowling?
我们知道很多关于...
We know too much about...
-保龄球  -不
- Bowling. - No.
-别的什么事  -保龄球
- It's something else. - Bowling.
那我先走了
So, I'm gonna take off.
-晚上见  -好的
- We'll see you tonight. - Yeah.
我们知道很多丘比特情侣的内幕
We know too much about the Cupid's Couple thing.
好吧
Oh! Okay.
你们一起来吧
Yeah, you can come.
看什么回来了
Look what's back.
-不  不  不  -来  来  来
- No, no, no. - Yes, yes, yes.
孩子们都出去了
Since the kids are out,
某人又受不了泡泡浴太多泡泡
and the bubble bath was a little too bubbly for some,
-我们干脆来点劲爆的  -不
- we're gonna finish strong with... - No.
脱衣舞表演
Striptease.
那听起来挺好玩的  我喜欢
That could be fun. I'd like that.
我也喜欢
I'd like that, too.
看你大显身手啦
See you strut your stuff.
-等等  我吗  -是啊
- Wait, me? - Yeah.
来段魔力麦克  亲爱的
Magic Mike me, baby.
《魔力麦克》:  电影  主角曾为脱衣舞男
琳  你不会想看的
Lin, you don't want that.
可我想啊
Oh, but I do.
真的吗  好吧
Really? Okay.
-那我就上了  -来吧
- Then I'll do it. - Yeah! Do it.
但如果我要跳的话
But if I'm gonna do this,
我可是来真的  琳
I'm gonna really do it, Lin.
-我会豁出去的  -鲍鲍
- I'm gonna go all in. - Bobby!
如果鲍勃・贝尔彻要跳脱衣舞
If Bob Belcher strips,
他一定会来真的
he's gonna strip serious.
怎么个真法  怎么跳
Like what? Like how?
疯狂地跳  你见所未见
Like crazy. Like you've never seen,
就像...  到你不想看的程度
like you wa... you won't even want it.
我跳不到20秒
After 20 seconds of my striptease,
你就  你就巴不得走开了
you're gonna... you'll want to leave.
我先要刮一下胸毛
I'm gonna go shave my chest
-然后选几首曲子  -来吧
- and pick out some music. - Let's do it!
-也许再刷个牙吧  -对
- Oh, maybe brush your teeth, too. - Oh, right.
-用牙线  好嘞  -好
- Maybe floss. Okay. - Yes.
各就各位
On your marks,
预备  开始
get set, go.
第五道  请别那样了
Lane five, don't do that.
什么  别扔保龄球吗
What, don't bowl?
感觉这颗能全中
Feels like there's a strike in here.
那张脸不如从前那般迷人了啊
Those cheeks aren't leaving me weak like they usually do.
-好球  -干得漂亮
- Hell, yeah! - Boom shaka-laka!
好兄弟
That's my boy!
快来
Get over here!
快来  快过来
Come on. Get over here.
齐克
Zeke.
达瑞尔
Oh, Darryl.
-来啊  -齐克
- Come on!  - Oh, Zeke!
-来啊 -齐克
- Come on!  - Zeke!
-你太粗鲁了  -来啊
- That's too rough. - Come on!
罗莎  别动
Rosa, don't move.
你背上有只大甲虫
There's a huge beetle on your back.
不
Oh, no.
我就喜欢你这样
I love it when you do that.
那是我们开的玩笑里我最喜欢的一个
That's-that's my favorite joke thing that we do.
够了
That's it!
我真忍不了了
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
你还好吗  蒂娜
Are you okay, Tina?
你那张脸现在不太像一张正常人类的脸
Yeah, your face does not look exactly normal for a human.
不  我不好
No, I'm not okay!
的确  老实说
Yeah, 'cause seriously,
你的表情是像
your expression is like...
这一切都不好  好吗
None of this is okay, okay?
我已经厌倦说谎了
I'm tired of lying.
你们需要知道真相
You need to know the truth.
蒂娜  你在做什么
Tina, what are you doing?
-我滴孩啊  -各位
- Oh, boy. - Everyone...
达瑞尔和我只是假装情侣
Darryl and I only pretended to be a couple,
好让他能成功钓上罗莎
so he could trick Rosa into dating him.
条件是他教我数学
And he would tutor me in math,
但其实也没教多少
but we didn't get around to much of that.
我们骗了你们  你们都上当了
We lied to you, and you all fell for it.
真奇怪  我要走了
That's weird. I'm outta here.
达瑞尔  这是真的吗
Darryl, is this true?
算是吧
Kind of?
好吧  那我算是再也不想见到你了
Well, then I kind of never want to see you again.
罗莎  回来
Rosa, come back!
蒂娜  你到底在做什么
Tina, what the hell are you doing?
我  我想
I-I guess...
-我想  -你想什么
- I guess... - You guess what?
我想我喜欢上你了
I guess I fell for you.
什么  但我们是假装的啊
What?! But we were pretending!
我没装
Well, I wasn't.
这关系真是扭曲啊
What a tangle-assed web we weave.
你喜欢上我了  怎么会  为什么
You fell for me? How? Why?
因为你做了好事说了好话
Because you did nice things and said nice things,
你还用我喜欢的方式搂过我
and we had our special side hug thing.
是你教我那么做的
You told me to do those things.
那你就不能一直扮演那个人吗
Well, can't you just be that guy?
不能  那个人根本不存在
No, that guy doesn't even exist.
但你也喜欢上我俩在一起时的那个蒂娜了
But you fell for the Tina I was when we were together.
不  我没有
No, I didn't.
我们假设你有  然后再往前推吧
Let's assume you did and work backwards from there.
不  蒂娜  我们喜欢的都是不同的东西
No, Tina, we don't even like the same stuff.
怎么不同
Sure we do.
-你喜欢数学  -不
- Do you like math? - No.
-电子游戏  -不
- And video games? - No...
-漫画  -不
- And comic books? - No.
-去自然博物馆吗  -不
- And going to the science museum? - No...
你知道谁喜欢那些吗
You know who likes all those things?
-谁  -罗莎
- Who? - Rosa!
罗莎全都喜欢
Rosa likes all that stuff!
天哪  你应该和罗莎在一起
Oh, God, you and Rosa should be together.
是的  我们应该
Yes, we should.
我拆散了一段美好的姻缘
I broke up a perfectly good relationship.
没错
Yes, you did.
我得让你俩重归于好
I need to get you two back together.
没错
Yes, you do.
老天  但愿我
Oh, boy. I hope I'm as good
撮合人的伎俩
at getting you guys back together
和我拆散人的伎俩一样好
as I was at breaking you up.
快去  去去去去
Go, go, go, go, go!
你好慢啊
You're taking forever in there.
可别把我的婴儿油给用光了
You better not be using all my baby oil.
好  我出来了
Okay, I'm coming out.
我本来想除个毛的  但只除了一半
I started to shave, but I stopped.
所以别看我的背
So don't look at my back.
好吧  我放音乐咯
Okay. Should I hit play, or...?
先别
Not yet.
我去  天呐
Oh, G... Oh, my God.
好紧啊  可以了
That's really tight. Okay now.
放吧
Now, go.
派对时间
Party time.
哟  哟  哟
Well, well, well.
有人...
Did someone...
-等我一下  -你还好吗
- Just give me a second. - You all right?
-很好  我马上回来  -好吧
- All right, let me just come right back. - Okay.
-去吧去吧  -先关一下音乐
- All right, go, go... - Just stop the music for a second.
-我马上出来  -好吧
- I'll be right back. - All right.
-我把脸侧过去  -开始吧
- I'm gonna look away. - All right put it on.
-我准备好了  准备好了  -开始
- I'm ready, I'm ready. - Here we go and play.
嗨  美女
Hey, there, lady.
有人点了外卖吗
Did someone order take out,
脱衣秀外卖
or should I say take off?
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
这个怎么样
How do you like that?
你喜欢吗
Oh, you like it?
-喜欢  -这才刚开始呢
- Yeah! - Well, it's just getting started.
咱淫荡起来
Let's get it down and dirty.
快脱  宝贝儿
Take it off, baby!
好咧
Yeah!
这样你感觉如何
How's this working for you?
这只是我的第一个动作
'Cause this is my one move.
-通通秀出来  -看咱扭臀
- Give it to mama. - Let's orbit the Earth.
看咱扭臀
Let's orbit the Earth.
我喜欢  扭得很圆嘛
I like it. It's circular.
好圆  我都要晕了
Round. I'm getting dizzy.
没错
Yeah, yeah.
我练了好久的
No, this is what I practiced.
现在换个方向
Let's go the other way.
来个逆时针的
Going counter-clockwise.
太恶心了
You're terrible!
有没有听到什么
Did you just hear something?
没  继续
Nah, nah, keep going.
应该是歌里的  继续嘛
I think it's in the song. Keep going.
能把衣服穿上不  巨婴
Put on some clothes, big boy!
天呐
Oh, my God.
窗帘没拉
The curtain's open.
-天  -你那背上是个啥
- Oh, God. - What happened to your back?
没人想看好吗
Nobody wants to see that.
我想
Hey! I do!
抱歉  我在给我老婆
Sorry. I was doing a striptease
跳脱衣舞庆祝情人日
for my wife for Valentine's Day, all right?
情人节早就过了
Valentine's Day was days ago.
得了吧
Give it up.
好吧
All right, fine.
我把窗帘拉上
I'm closing the curtains.
别啊
Oh, no.
我去  拉不上了
Crap. They're not closing.
对不起  鲍鲍
I'm sorry, Bobby.
情人周什么的也许不是好主意
This Valentine's Days thing was a bad idea.
我们好差劲
We just stink at it.
-真差劲  -别别  琳  知道吗
- We stink. No, no, Lin, you know what?
我说了要做  就一定会做
I said I was gonna do it, so I'm gonna do it.
好吗  我会做的
All right? I'm gonna do it.
-真的吗  -坐回去  琳
- Yeah? - Take a seat, Lin.
我要重新上桌子了
I'm going back on the table.
来吧
Do it!
扭臀  扭臀
Orbit the Earth. Orbit the Earth.
鲍鲍  快来转我
Oh, Bobby, spin me right round.
我要下来了  宝贝儿
It's all coming off, baby!
白痴
Ass!
罗莎  罗莎  你在这儿呢
Rosa? Rosa? There you are.
我叫了你这么多次
It's okay you didn't say anything back
你都不答应我  对此你不用感到内疚
when I called your name all those times.
听我说  达瑞尔说喜欢我是骗人的
Look, Darryl lied about liking me,
但他说喜欢你却是真的
but he didn't lie about liking you.
你应该再给他一次机会
You gotta give him another chance.
为什么
Why should I?
因为达瑞尔和我在一起是对很好的假情侣
Because Darryl and I were a great fake couple,
和你在一起就可以是绝配的真情侣
but you and Darryl can be a great real couple.
我为啥要和他做真情侣
And why would we be a great real couple?
因为你现在虽然看着我
'Cause you're looking at me
手上却还在疯狂地轰炸那些蜥蜴
and you're still blasting lizard guys like crazy.
不是蜥蜴  是蛇
They're not lizards. They're snakes.
更确切地说  他们是
And technically, they're actually
-黑暗城堡的恶魔  -黑暗城堡的恶魔
- demons from the black castle. - Demons from the black castle.
我来这儿是想躲你的
I came here to get away from you.
你要真想躲达瑞尔
An arcade might not be the best place
就不该来游戏厅
to get away from Darryl.
罗莎  你愿不愿意和达瑞尔
Rosa, will you press two-players
来一局双人战  看看结局如何
with Darryl for one game and see how it goes?
不  不愿意
No. No way.
他骗我喜欢上了他
He tricked me into liking him.
不  我现在才知道  被骗的
No. I realize now the only people
其实是我和达瑞尔
that got tricked were me and Darryl.
你和达瑞尔
You and Darryl?
我骗自己喜欢上了
I tricked myself into falling
一个我自己打造出来的达瑞尔
for a version of Darryl that I created.
达瑞尔骗自己
Then Darryl tricked himself
有勇气和你说话
into being confident enough to talk to you.
让我自己待会儿  行吗
Leave me alone, all right?
算了蒂娜  罗莎回到她自己的阵营去了
Forget it, Tina; Rosa's back to being out of my league.
该死  根本没有什么阵营
Damn it, there are no leagues!
保龄球阵营赛将在九号至12号球道进行
League bowling will now begin on lanes nine through 12.
好吧  除了保龄球里的阵营
Okay, except bowling leagues.
但人与人之间不应该有阵营
But there shouldn't be people leagues.
但确实有  蒂娜  这就是事实
But there are, Tina; That's just how it is.
是你自己以为你配不上罗莎
You're the one who thought you were out of Rosa's league.
罗莎可没这么想
Not Rosa.
难道就因为你二年级时在滑梯上撒了尿吗
Why, because you peed on the slide in second grade?
就你自己还一直记得这事儿
You're the only one still holding onto that.
没啊  我记得可清楚了
No, I totally remember.
好吧  就你和乔丝玲  还有我
Okay, so you and Jocelyn, and I remember, too.
达瑞尔  重点是  如果你喜欢罗莎
The point is, Darryl, if you liked Rosa,
那你就应该主动和她说话
then you should have just gone and talked to her.
即使她还记得你撒尿的事儿
Even if she remembered the pee thing.
你能  呃  别再提那事儿了吗
Could you just, um, stop bringing that up? Right.
-你说撒尿那事儿吗  -是的
- The pee thing? - Yes.
罗莎  对不起
Rosa, I'm sorry.
我应该告诉你我喜欢你的
I should have just told you I liked you.
是的  你确实该那样
Yes, you should have.
所以你们到底要不要玩双人战
So will you guys press two player already?
你疯了吗  我可是黑暗城堡级别的
Are you crazy? I'm on the black castle level!
她可是黑暗城堡级别的
She's on the black castle level!
我们同一时间说了一样的话
We said the same thing at the same time.
你知道那级别可以提升攻击力吗
You know there's a hidden power-up on that level.
真的吗
Really?
-要不要我教你  -好的
- Want me to show you? - Yes.
他俩就像马里奥和路易吉[超级玛丽兄弟]
They're like Mario and Luigi.
他们好爱对方
They're so in love.
我天  蒂娜启发我了
Dang it, Tina's inspired me.
-乔丝玲  -什么
- Jocelyn? - What?
你能挪一下地儿吗
Could you scooch out of the way?
我想找那位租鞋的小姐约会
I want to ask out that shoe rental woman.
她看着像有35了  齐克
She's like 35, Zeke.
手上还戴着戒指
And she's wearing a wedding ring.
那又怎样  没有什么阵营
So? No leagues.
最大的敌人是我自己
I'm the only one holding me back,
因为我觉得自己是弓形腿
because I think I'm too bow-legged.
但其实我并不是  我弓得刚刚好
But I'm not. Just the right amount.
现在我要摇摆过去约她了
So let me waddle over here and just ask her out right now.
嗨  宝贝儿
Hey, baby!
任务成功
Well, mission accomplished.
绝对的
Absolutely.
除了小吉米  他抛弃你了
Except that Jimmy Jr. Ran out on you.
而且你数学测验估计也得挂了
And you're probably gonna fail that math test.
不  小吉米我可能追不上了
No. I may have failed Jimmy Jr.,
但数学测验我可不会挂
but I'm not going to fail the math test.
我要拿A
I'm gonna ace it.
再不济
Or at least get a B.
我也得拿个B
In which case I'll "Bace" It.
该死
Nuts.
我拿了个D
I "Daced" It.
爱情补习  数学也补习
Remedial at love, remedial at math.
小吉米  原来你数学也很烂
Jimmy Jr., I didn't know you were bad at math.
-非一般地烂  -要跟我一起共患"烂"吗
- Yeah, real bad. - You want to be bad at math together?
-好啊  没问题  -棒
- Yeah, okay. Sure. - Yes.
*姑娘*
*Girl... *
*多希望和你共度每一课堂*
*I wish you were in all my classes*
*课堂*
*Classes *
*当我们亲吻对方*
*And when we kiss *
*我们的眼镜也碰上*
*We hit our glasses *
*镜片*
*Glasses *
*让我们慢舞一曲*
*Now let's slow dance *
*像蜂蜜糖浆*
*Like molasses*
*蜜糖一般*
*Molasses *
*像蜂蜜...糖浆*
*Like mo-oh-oh-la-a-a-a-a-a-asses. *
谢谢大家  晚安
Thank you, good night!